https://www.connfireworks.com/privacy-policy.html

ACCOUNT CONTACT MY CART
Home/ Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to protect your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Sales to Minors We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian. You must be 21 or older to purchase fireworks. The Information We Collect This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the connfireworks.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are Name, Address, Email address, Phone number, Credit/Debit Card Information. On some pages, you can submit information about other people. The Way We Use Information We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. Information you provide to us to create a gift card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. We never share or sell your personal information with any third parties. Our Commitment To Data Security To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Your personal information is secured via SSL (Secure Socket Layer) Technology. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. How You Can Access Or Correct Information You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us and answering a few questions. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. How To Contact Us Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 860-349-9747 or send us an email at info@connfireworks.com.
Quick Selections
Aerial Products - Cased Wholesale Shop By Brand Connecticut Fireworks Retail Outlet Rockets Fountains Fuse Gender Reveal Fountains Ground Products Novelties Smoke Devices Sparklers Specials Connecticut Legal
Assortments Incoming Fireworks
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Copyright © 2020 Dapkus Fireworks Inc.. | Provided by The Scribbit
